[
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¦",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø³Ø¹ÙˆØ¯ÙŠØ©"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙ„Ø§ÙŠØ§Øª Ø§Ù„Ù…ØªØ­Ø¯Ø©"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¦",
    "response": "ÙƒÙ†Ø¯Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù…Ù…Ù„ÙƒØ© Ø§Ù„Ù…ØªØ­Ø¯Ø©"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡·",
    "response": "ÙØ±Ù†Ø³Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø£Ù„Ù…Ø§Ù†ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹",
    "response": "Ø¥ÙŠØ·Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¸",
    "response": "Ø¥Ø³Ø¨Ø§Ù†ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡º",
    "response": "Ø±ÙˆØ³ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡³",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ØµÙŠÙ†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡µ",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§Ø¨Ø§Ù†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡º",
    "response": "Ø£Ø³ØªØ±Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡³",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù‡Ù†Ø¯"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡·",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¨Ø±Ø§Ø²ÙŠÙ„"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø£Ø±Ø¬Ù†ØªÙŠÙ†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡´",
    "response": "ÙƒÙˆÙ„ÙˆÙ…Ø¨ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡½",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù…ÙƒØ³ÙŠÙƒ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬",
    "response": "Ù…ØµØ±"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡·",
    "response": "ØªØ±ÙƒÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡·",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙŠÙˆÙ†Ø§Ù†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡­",
    "response": "Ø³ÙˆÙŠØ³Ø±Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡´",
    "response": "Ø±ÙˆÙ…Ø§Ù†ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡±",
    "response": "Ø¨ÙˆÙ„Ù†Ø¯Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡¸",
    "response": "ØµØ±Ø¨ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø³ÙˆÙŠØ¯"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡´",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù†Ø±ÙˆÙŠØ¬"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡°",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¯Ù†Ù…Ø§Ø±Ùƒ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡±",
    "response": "Ù‡ÙˆÙ„Ù†Ø¯Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø¨Ù„Ø¬ÙŠÙƒØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡¹",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù†Ù…Ø³Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¿",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ØªØ´ÙŠÙƒ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡­ğŸ‡º",
    "response": "Ù‡Ù†ØºØ§Ø±ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¨Ø±ØªØºØ§Ù„"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø¨ÙŠØ±Ùˆ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡±",
    "response": "ØªØ´ÙŠÙ„ÙŠ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡»ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "ÙÙ†Ø²ÙˆÙŠÙ„Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¿ğŸ‡¦",
    "response": " Ø£ÙØ±ÙŠÙ‚ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¹",
    "response": "Ø¥Ø«ÙŠÙˆØ¨ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¨",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¥ÙƒÙˆØ§Ø¯ÙˆØ±"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡¿",
    "response": "Ù†ÙŠÙˆØ²ÙŠÙ„Ù†Ø¯Ø§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡¬",
    "response": "Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠØ±ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡¿",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¬Ø²Ø§Ø¦Ø±"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡¦",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ù…ØºØ±Ø¨"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡³",
    "response": "ØªÙˆÙ†Ø³"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬",
    "response": "Ù…ØµØ±"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡±ğŸ‡§",
    "response": "Ù„Ø¨Ù†Ø§Ù†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡´",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø£Ø±Ø¯Ù†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¾",
    "response": "Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¶",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¹Ø±Ø§Ù‚"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¶ğŸ‡¦",
    "response": "Ù‚Ø·Ø±"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¥Ù…Ø§Ø±Ø§Øª"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡¼",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙƒÙˆÙŠØª"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡´ğŸ‡²",
    "response": "Ø¹Ù…Ø§Ù†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡­",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„Ø¨Ø­Ø±ÙŠÙ†"
  },
  {
    "question": "ğŸ‡¾ğŸ‡ª",
    "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙŠÙ…Ù†"
  }
]
